A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865 (APA 293)., Extent: XX cubic feet. (Box XX-XX)
  - Vouchers (Barksdale's and Petersburg Warehouses), 1802 Sept 30. (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1802 Oct 6. (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1802 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1802 May 22. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1802 May 28. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1802 Oct 18. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1802 Oct 19. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1802 Oct 23. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1802 Nov 6. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham Warehouses), 1802 Nov 10. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1802 Nov 10. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1802 Nov 20. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1802 Dec 13. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole, Machodack and Port Conway Warehouses), 1802 Dec 15. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1803 Jan 10. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1803 Jan 14. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1803 Mar 12. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1803 Apr 8. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1803 Apr 11. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Swan Creek Warehouse), 1803 May 12. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1803 June 10. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Martin's Warehouse), 1803 June 10. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Manchester and Trent's Warehouses), 1803 Sept 10. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1803 Sept 19. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (King George Counties Warehouses), 1803. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Bolling's and Petersburg Warehouses), 1803 Sept 30. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1803 Sept 30. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1803. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Amherst Warehouse), 1803 Oct 24. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1803 Oct 26. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1803 Nov 9. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1803 Nov 17. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouse), 1803 Nov 23. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1803 Dec 3. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1803 Dec 6. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1803 Dec 14. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1803 Dec 15. (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Brookneal Warehouse), 1803 Dec 19. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1803 Dec 28. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1804 Jan 13. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1804 Feb 2. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1804 Feb 3. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1804 May 14. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1804 June 6. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg and Prince George County Warehouses), 1804 Aug 8. (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1804 Aug 16. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's, Fredericksburg and Royston's Warehouses), 1804 Sept 20. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1804 Sept 24. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Jamestown Warehouse), 1804 Sept 29. (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's, Shockoe Warehouses), 1804 Oct 8. (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1804 Oct 10. (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg and Prince George County Warehouses), 1804 Oct 16. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg, Martin's, and Spring Warehouses), 1804 Oct 17. (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1804 Oct 23. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Swann Creek and Tye River Warehouses), 1804 Nov 1. (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1804 Nov 2. (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Manchester and Trent's Warehouses), 1804 Nov 16. (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1804 Nov 16. (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1804 Nov 20. (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Dymer's and Indian Creek Warehouses), 1804 Dec 6. (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1804 Dec 6. (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1804 Dec 8. (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1804 Dec 11. (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Brookneal Warehouse), 1804 Dec 31. (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's and Davis Warehouses), 1805 Jan 12. (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1805 Feb 13. (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Layton's Warehouse), 1805 Feb 16. (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1805 Feb 20. (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1805 Apr 3. (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1805 May 9. (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (unknown Warehouse), 1805 July 18. (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1805 Sept 20. (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Dunn's, Fredericksburg and Royston's Warehouses), 1805 Sept 24. (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1805 Sept 25. (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1805 Sept 27. (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Lynch's Spring and Martin's Warehouse), 1805 Oct 9. (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1805 Oct 17. (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1805 Oct 22. (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1805 Nov 14. (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Vouchers (Dinwiddie County and Petersburg Warehouses), 1805 Dec 6. (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's, Gibson's and Machodack Warehouses), 1805 Dec 9. (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1805 Dec 12. (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1805 Dec 13. (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Vouchers (Brookneal Warehouse), 1805 Dec 16. (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Vouchers (Powhatan Warehouse), 1806 Jan 7. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1806 Jan 27. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Lynch's, Martin's, and Spring Warehouses), 1806 Feb 7. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1806 Apr 28. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Warehouse), 1806 May 19. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Swann Creek and Tye River Warehouses), 1806 June 2. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1806 July 15. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County Warehouses), 1806 Sept 1. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1806 Sept 6. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1806 Sept 15. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1806 Sept 15. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Randolph's and Townes Warehouses), 1806 Sept 22. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1806 Sept 23. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Spotsylvania County Warehouses), 1806 Sept 23. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Machodack Warehouse), 1806 Sept 29. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1806 Sept 29. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1806 Sept 30. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1806 Sept 30. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Catpoint Warehouse), 1806 Oct 1. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1806 Oct 2. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Powhatan, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1806 Oct 14. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1806 Oct 18. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Moore's Warehouse), 1806 Nov 10. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg / Prince George County Warehouses), 1806 Nov 14. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Lynche's and Spring Warehouses), 1806 Nov 18. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Street Warehouse), 1806 Nov 22. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1806 Dec 1. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Quantico Warehouse), 1806 Dec 24. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1807 Jan 6. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1807 Jan 21. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1807 Feb 4. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Dunkirk Warehouse), 1807 Feb 16. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1807 Apr 8. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1807 July 13. (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1807 Aug 10. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1807 Sept 18. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Brookneal Warehouse), 1807 Sept 21. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County Warehouses), 1807 Sept 22. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1807 Sept 29. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Townes Warehouse), 1807 Sept 20. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1807 Oct 1. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Deane's Warehouse), 1807 Oct 1. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1807 Oct 1. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Petesburg / Prince George County Warehouses), 1807 Oct 16. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Dinwiddie County Warehouse), 1807 Oct 24. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Cabell's, Liberty, Lynch's and Spring Warehouses), 1807 Nov 13. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Blackwater and Planter's Warehouses), 1807 Nov 13. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Powhatan, Rockett's, and Shockoe Warehouses), 1807 Nov 14. (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Oaks Warehouse), 1807 Dec 8. (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1807 Dec 8. (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1807 Dec 14. (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1807 Dec 16. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1807 Dec 16. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole, Gibson's and Machodack Warehouses), 1807 Dec 17. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1807 Dec 17. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1807 Dec 17. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg and Royston's Warehouses), 1807 Dec 18. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Boswell's Warehouse), 1807 Dec 28. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1808 Jan 11. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1808 Feb 6. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1808 Mar 16. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Coan Warehouse), 1808 Mar 30. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1808 Apr 9. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Prince George County / Petersburg Warehouses), 1808 July 21. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Canon's Warehouse), 1808 Sept 19. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County Warehouses), 1808 Sept 19. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1808 Sept 26. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1808 Sept 26. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Coan Warehouse), 1808 Sept 27. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Camden, Swan Creek and Tye River Warehouses), 1808 Sept 30. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Powhatan, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1808 Oct 7. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1808 Oct 8. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Henderson and Randolph's Warehouses), 1808 Oct 8. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1808 Oct 10. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1808 Oct 10. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's Warehouse), 1808 Oct 13. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Tye River Warehouse), 1808 Oct 18. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Moore's Warehouse), 1808 Oct 19. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Oaks Warehouse), 1808 Oct 19. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1808 Oct 19. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1808 Oct 20. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (West Brook Warehouse), 1808 Oct 20. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Boswell's Warehouse), 1808 Oct 21. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Cedar Point Warehouse), 1808 oct 21. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (West Hill Warehouse), 1808 Oct 28. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg, Liberty, Martin's, and Friend's Warehouses), 1808 Oct 29. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1808 Oct 31. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1808 Nov 1. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's, Fredericksburg, and Royston's Warehouses), 1808 Nov 2. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1808 Nov 2. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchester Warehouses), 1808 Nov 11. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Warehouse), 1808 Nov 14. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Davies Warehouse), 1808 Nov 14. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1808 Nov 14. (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Blandford Warehouse), 1808 Nov 17. (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Nicholas' Warehouse), 1808 Nov 22. (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Nicholas' Warehouse), 1808 Dec 8. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Nicholas' Warehouse), 1808 Dec 8. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1808 Dec 10. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Dinwiddie County / Petersburg Warehouses), 1808 Dec 15. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1808 Dec 15. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg and Falmouth Warehouses), 1808 Dec 19. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1809 Jan 4. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook Warehouse), 1809 Jan 6. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1809 Jan 23. (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Deane's Warehouse), 1809 Feb 2. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1809 Feb 7. (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1809 Apr 10. (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1809 Apr 18. (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1809 July 1. (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Liberty Warehouse), 1809 July 28. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Campbell County Warehouses), 1809 Sept 27. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County Warehouses), 1809 Oct 3. (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1809 Oct 3. (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Powhatan, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1809 Oct 9. (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1809 Oct 21. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1809 Oct 21. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Henderson and Randolph's Warehouses), 1809 Oct 24. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1809 Oct 30. (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's, Royston's and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1809 Oct 31. (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg and Falmouth Warehouses), 1809 Nov 1. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Swan Creek and Tye River Warehouses), 1809 Nov 1. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Deane's Warehouse), 1809 Nov 6. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1809 Nov 7. (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (McRae's Warehouse), 1809 nov 10. (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchester Warehouses), 1809 Nov 29. (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's Warehouse), 1809 Nov 29. (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1809 Dec 1. (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1809 Dec 4. (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Deane's Warehouse), 1809 Dec 16. (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1809 Dec 19. (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1809 Dec 20. (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Jan 2. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1810 jan 30. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (McRae's Warehouse), 1810 Feb 7. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Feb 10. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Feb 12. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Mar 10. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Powhatan Warehouses), 1810 Apr 25. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 May 12. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 May 15. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 June 6. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Cedarpoint Warehouse), 1810 June 22. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Cedarpoint, Prince George County, Petersburg Warehouses), 1810 July 5. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Sept 5. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1810 Sept 25. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses - Blackwater, Friend's, Lynch's and Martin's), 1810 Oct 1. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1810 Oct 5. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1810 Oct 10. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1810 Oct 11. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1810 Oct 11. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1810 Oct 13. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1810 Oct 19. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1810 Oct 23. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Quantico Warehouse), 1810 Oct 23. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's, Royston's and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1810 Oct 29. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1810 Oct 31. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1810 Dec 10. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1811 Jan 11. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1811 Feb 4. (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1811 Feb 8. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1811 June 14. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1811 June 26. (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Seabrook's Warehouse), 1811 July 16. (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1811 Sept 20. (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1811 Oct 11. (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 14. (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 17. (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Chesterfield County, Dinwiddie County and Petersburg Warehouses), 1811 Oct 18. (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Manchester Warehouses), 1811 Oct 21. (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1811 Oct 21. (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Boswell's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 22. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1811 Oct 22. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1811 Oct 23. (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (McRae's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 24. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1811 Oct 25. (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Blandford's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 26. (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook's Warehouse), 1811 Oct 26. (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Oaks Warehouse), 1811 Oct 26. (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Westbrook Warehouse), 1811 Oct 26. (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Davis' Warehouse), 1811 Oct 28. (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1811 Oct 28. (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1811 Nov 1. (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1811 Nov 2. (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Peterburg Warehouses), 1811 Nov 2. (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Moore's Warehouse), 1811 Nov 8. (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1811 Nov 8. (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Cedarpoint Warehouse), 1811 Nov 28. (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1811 Dec 4. (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1812 Jan 9. (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1812 Jan 29. (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1812 Apr 14. (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Westhill Warehouse), 1812 Apr 14. (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1812 June 12. (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1812 June 13. (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1812 Aug 11. (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1812 Aug 31. (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg Warehouses), 1812 Sept 28. (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1812 Oct 1. (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1812 Oct 11. (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1812 Oct 20. (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Boswell's Warehouse), 1812 Oct 24. (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1812 Oct 27. (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Peterburg Warehouses), 1812 Oct 27. (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1812 Oct 28. (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Fluvanna County Warehouses), 1812 Nov 3. (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's, and Manchester Warehouses), 1812 Nov 17. (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook Warehouse), 1812 Nov 30. (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Cross Street Warehouse), 1812 Nov 30. (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1812 Nov 30. (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1812 Dec 1. (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Davis' Warehouse), 1812 Dec 21. (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Blandford Warehouse), 1813 Jan 2. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1813 Jan 13. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Westhill Warehouse), 1813 Jan 13. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1813 Jan 18. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1813 Mar 13. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (McRae's Warehouse), 1813 May 27. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1813 June 14. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1813 Aug 23. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Campbell County Warehouses), 1813 Sept 23. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (James River Canal Warehouses), 1813 Oct 6. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1813 Oct 19. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1813 Oct 19. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1813 Oct 22. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1813 Oct 25. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Randolph's Warehouses), 1813 Oct 27. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouses), 1813 oct 27. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Bethel and Madison Warehouses), 1813 Oct 29. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1813 Oct 29. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1813 Nov 3. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1813 Nov 8. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouses), 1813 Nov 26. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Cedarpoint Warehouse), 1814 Jan 8. (Box 11, Folder 18)